The
length of the long square plate is 10 mm and the height is 250 mm.
Next, we will make a knot.
To make a knot, we need to reduce the strength of the particle and check the thickness of the collision.
The current thickness of the collision is 2.5.
You don't need to adjust it.
Use the fixed needle tool to fix the needles in each row.
In the process of simulation, use the fixed needle tool to turn the rectangular plate into a circle and then make a knot.
In the process of knotting, press the W key to add a fixed needle.
Press the W key again to click on the fixed needle.
You can delete the fixed needle.
Now we are back home.
In the process of knotting, we need to pause the simulation.
In this way, we will record the state of the simulation to prevent the knotting.
Thank you.
Place it around the rope and adjust its size.
Change its fabric physics attribute to default fabric simulation.
The rectangular board needs to be wrapped around the rope.
Set up two internal lines.
Use the folding arrangement tool to fold.
After folding, sew it together.
Since the board is small, you need to reduce the structure of the barrier.
Use the folding arrangement tool to fold.
Since the rope is a virtual model, the surface is 3mm,
we need to modify it to be 0mm.
After that, we need to delete the folding arrangement.
After that, we need to modify it to be 0mm.
Because the diameter is wider,
The board is directly slipped.
Here you can cancel it.
Reduce its particle diameter to 1.
There is a seam line mark on the seam side.
If you want no mark, you can delete the seam line.
Because it is tightly packed, it can be divided into three boards.
The seam line marks can also delete the seam line pattern.
Set different shrinkage to tighten it.
Adjust the shape of the plastic.
If the shape is too tight, it will be difficult to insert the wheel.
For some reason, the wheel is empty, so it is difficult to insert the wheel.
If the shape of the plate is too tight, it is difficult to insert the wheel.
I will open the disc.
I can see the moves of it.
Direct it to the bottom and bend the wheel.
The wheel moves in the direction of the actual center of the wheel from the first point.
When the wheel is moved to the center of the wheel, the wheel becomes grilling.
Get to the bottom.
Line up one by one.
Thank you.